Guide to the Caterpillar (Sherman Oaks, CA) Archive ca.1957-1987 MSS.010
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Caterpillar Issues
  - Issue No.2: manuscript layout, pg.91-112., undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Issue No.2: manuscript layout, pg.113-54, back cover., undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Issue No.3/4: rough sketches, table of contents., undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Issue No.3/4: manuscript, pg.1-55, 93-148., undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Issue No.3/4: manuscript, pg.149-50, 154-80, 183-208., undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Issue No.3/4: manuscript, pg.209-70, back cover., undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Issue No.3/4: page proofs, pg.1-55, 93-146., undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Issue No.3/4: page proofs, pg.149-94, 200-74., undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Issue No.3/4: proofs "Blues"., undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Issue No.5: front cover photo., undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Issue No.5: manuscript, pg.1-71., undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Issue No.5: manuscript, pg.72-159., undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Issue No.5: page proofs, art work., undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Issue No.6: manuscript, pg.1-46., undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Issue No.6: manuscript, pg.50-76, 93-103., undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Issue No.6: manuscript, pg.104-58., undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Issue No.6: page proofs, front & back cover, mock-ups., undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Issue No.6: page proofs, advertisements., undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Issue No.6: page proofs., undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Issue No.7: manuscript, pg.11-88., undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Issue No.7: manuscript, pg.89-252., undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Issue No.7: art work, table of contents., undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Issue No.8/9: manuscript layout, pg.1-126., undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Issue No.8/9: manuscript layout, pg.127-256., undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Issue No.8/9: art work, table of contents., undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Issue No.8/9: subscription offer/artwork., undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Issue No.8/9: advertisements., undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Issue No.8/9: Spero, Nancy, photographs., undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Issue No.8/9: illustrations(photographs), undated (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Issue No.10: table of contents., undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Issue No.10: manuscript, pg.6-158., undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Issue No.10: manuscript, pg.164-252., undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Issue No.10: manuscript layout, pg.1-141., undated (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Issue No.10: Cover Design by Robert Lavigne, undated (Box 24)
  - Issue No.10: manuscript layout, pg.142-255., undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Issue No.11: table of contents., undated (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Issue No.11: manuscript, pg.15-153., undated (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Issue No.11: manuscript, pg.1-160., undated (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Issue No.12: table of contents., undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Issue No.12: manuscript, pg.2-216., undated (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Issue No.12: manuscript layout, pg.1-112., undated (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Issue No.12: manuscript layout, pg.113-224., undated (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Issue No.13: table of contents, cover artwork., undated (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Issue No.13: manuscript, pg.1-87., undated (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Issue No.13: manuscript, pg.88-160., undated (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Issue No.13: manuscript layout, pg.1-160., undated (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Issue No.14: table of contents, cover artwork., undated (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Issue No.14: manuscript, 2-160., undated (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Issue No.14: manuscript layout, pg.1-160., undated (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Issue No.15/16: table of contents, cover artwork., undated (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Issue No.15/16: manuscript, pg.2-200., undated (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Issue No.15/16: manuscript, pg.212-301., undated (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Issue No.15/16: Kitaj, R.B. photograph, pg.201., undated (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Issue No.15/16: manuscript layout, pg.1-135., undated (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Issue No.15/16: manuscript layout, pg.136-303., undated (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Issue No.17: table of contents., undated (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Issue No.17: manuscript, pg.3-127., undated (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Issue No.17: manuscript layout, pg.1-127., undated (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Issue No.18: table of contents., undated (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Issue No.18: manuscript, pg.18-127., undated (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Issue No.18: back cover, art work., undated (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Issue No.18: manuscript layout, pg.1-127., undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Issue No.19: table of contents, art work., undated (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Issue No.19: manuscript, pg.1-134., undated (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Issue No.19: manuscript layout, pg.1-148., undated (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Issue No.20: table of contents, art work., undated (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Issue No.20: manuscript, pg.2-112., undated (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Issue No.20: manuscript, pg.113-175., undated (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Issue No.20, manuscript layout, pg.1-176., undated (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Author/Artist index for issues 1-20., undated (Box 22, Folder 85)
- Series IV: Caterpillar Galleys
  Scope and Contents note
  Box 23 Oversize
  - Issue No.1: tape 1-7, sheets 1-29., undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Issue No.3/4: folio sheets., undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Issue No.5: folio sheets., undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Drawings and Publicity (including Grauer, Scibella, Williams), undated (Box 23, Folder 4)